emastered.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | eMastered Instant Audio Mastering

Thank you for using eMastered (hereafter also referred to as “the service,” the platform”, the site,” “the application,” and “the system”) and taking the time to understand our privacy policy.  We have made this policy to discuss the information that eMastered collects from you, how it uses this information, and the extent to which it protects this information.

## What personal information does eMastered collect from you?

In order to use eMastered some information will be collected from you, namely your age, email address, and other relevant information, which is needed to help you create an account and to allow us to improve the platform and offer a better experience to its users.  We also analyze and collect information on the device through which you visit the platform, including the type of device used, the web browser used, the day / time the application was visited and the IP address of said device.  We also collect geographical data from your device if your location services function is turned on within your device.  Information is also collected regarding how you use our platform, namely which pages and tabs / services you access and for how long.  Lastly, eMastered makes use of third party login credentials through social media accounts such as Facebook and Twitter.  By using that functionality you agree to share information similar in nature to the information listed above that is available from those accounts.

## At what point does eMastered collect your personal information?

We collect information from you when you:

## 

  * Sign up for an account or post to a third party social media account through the application

  * Sign up for a paid service or offering

  * Opt in or subscribe to a newsletter

  * Submit or reply to a written survey

  * Sign up for our forum / blog

  * Download our plugins or other free offerings

  * Visit different pages or sections of the platform

  * Enter other information on the platform

## How does eMastered use your information?

The information we collect is intended to help us deliver a superior experience to you on the platform.  The specific uses for this information include but are not limited to the following:

## 

  * To personalize user experiences and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

  * To analyze and improve the application’s aesthetic, design, and feature set in order to better serve you and our mission.

  * To allow us to properly understand and better respond to your customer service needs and requests.

  * To quickly process your transactions.

  * To send email updates regarding changes to the application, our policies, terms of service, or to update you on other products and services we are currently offering or plan to offer in the future.

  * To authenticate your account and payment preferences.

  * To analyze the types of media being uploaded to eMastered in order to allow us to better understand your needs from the platform.

## How do we protect visitor information?

Visitor information is protected in several ways, as your security is important to us.  Financial transactions authorized by you from within the platform are processed through a third party provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.  The sensitive / encrypted information you provide through the application is protected with SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology, and we regularly run Malware Scanning.  Your personal information itself is contained behind our secured network, which is designed to be only accessible by those who have special access rights to this infrastructure and who additionally respect the right to keep this personal information confidential.  We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

## What are ‘cookies’ and do we use them?

Cookies are tracking mechanisms sent through your web browser that allow a platform or site provider to remember certain information about your browser, along with storing preferences on the site itself.  We use cookies in an effort to compile site interaction and traffic information.  This information is meant to provide us with insights into how our platform is being used and reached, which allows us to improve the platform through optimization and by adding new features, along with tracking advertisements. In some cases we employ trusted third-party services that analyze and track this data for us.

It is possible to turn off cookies entirely, or simply have your device alert you when a cookie is being used.  Each browser has a specific way to do this, but if you disable cookies then there is a possibility a portion of our application will not function as intended.

## Third-party links

There are times when third party content will be incorporated into our application and / or social media presence.  These can include third party web URLs, links, articles, products and / or other media.  The privacy policies of these third party entities are not overseen by us, thus eMastered assumes no liability or responsibility for the activities, content and / or information provided by these third parties.  We do however aim to protect the integrity of our application and welcome your thoughts and ideas about these sites and how they fit in with our mission and desired experience.

## Third-party Sharing of Information

Various arrangements and partnerships may be created between eMastered and other third parties.  These third parties may be allowed to access personally identifiable information in an attempt to provide to you information on services and products that we think you will find suitable.  This information can include but is not limited to your name, address, telephone number, email address, and other information gathered from social media accounts.  Personally identifiable information may also be given to third parties if it is used responsibly or if it helps us carry out business operations.  In the event of a merger, acquisition, sale, purchase, dissolution, corporate divestiture, or other similar transactions, personally identifiable information may be transferred in these cases.  Personally identifiable information may also be shared with parties associated with our website and those who run and /or oversee it, those who service our customers, and those who conduct our business with us.  Finally, personally identifiable information may be provided to third parties if the law requires us to do so under specific circumstances such as personal safety or court orders, or if it is required to uphold our or other’s rights / property / safety, or to enforce the policies on our site.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA requires websites and other online services to abide by and create privacy policies.  The policy must be recognizably placed on the platform or website to highlight what personally identifiable information is collected from users of the platform, with whom the information is shared, and under what circumstances the sharing occurs.  Under CalOPPA we have made this policy accessible on our website through our menu listed as “privacy,” and whenever the policy is changed users will be notified on the privacy page itself.  Users are able to visit our site anonymously should they choose.  In addition, any personal information created by users can be changed by emailing us.

## Is third-party behavioral tracking allowed on our site?

Third party behavioral tracking is allowed on the platform, with the intent to help us better understand the needs of our customers and to provide the best experience we can on the application.

## Do we specifically market to children under the age of 13, which is prohibited by COPPA (the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act)?

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13.

## How does eMastered operate with regard to Fair Information Practice Principles (FIPPS)?

We take the Fair Information Practice Principles seriously, and should a data breach occur we will notify the users via email within a reasonable timeframe.

## English is the authoritative version, translations are provided for convenience and may not be current.
